Narrator: Nadine, France
Nadine: I have breakfast in a great café near my office.
I have a croissant and coffee – an espresso with hot milk.
Mmmm. I love breakfast!
It’s my favourite meal.
Narrator: Pablo, Argentina
Pablo: I have breakfast at home, but I don’t have a big breakfast.
I have fruit and yogurt, and sometimes toast.
It’s a healthy breakfast.
That’s a good thing at the beginning of the day.
Narrator: Rob, UK
Rob: I don’t eat in the morning – I’m not hungry.
I just have a coffee at work.
But I have lunch early, at about 12.30.
Narrator: Sakura, Japan
Sakura: I really like breakfast.
It’s an important meal for Japanese people.
I have breakfast at home with my family.
We have a traditional breakfast.
It isn’t very different from lunch and dinner.
We have rice, fish, and miso soup and we drink green tea.
We don’t drink a lot of coffee in my family.